<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rossoskull.me</title>
    <description>Hey everyone! I am Jay Mistry, a sophomore at IIIT Vadodara. I got into coding a bit early in
 my life, and am loving it since then! I love learning new stuff, and building things that help 
 out me, and others. I believe in building a solution, rather than finding it someplace else. You 
 can know more about me on one of my social handles. Thanks for visiting!
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 22:32:08 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 22:32:08 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Journey Before IIITV</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone! Today I’ll discuss my journey - how it all started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I began my coding journey a bit early in my life, and since then, it’s been wonderful. I try to keep learning new things everyday. I also believe in application. As it is known, only knowledge, and no application leads that knowledge to waste. So, &lt;i&gt;Keep Learning&lt;/i&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started my journey in coding with &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/QBasic&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;QBASIC&lt;/a&gt;. As it’s name suggests, it’s for beginners. So I didn’t have a hard time with it. And with spending more time with it, I realised that I started to love Coding. The thought that I could possibly create &lt;b&gt;anything&lt;/b&gt; fascinated me. I felt “God-like”, we can say. And so it began - my journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that, I started building simple web pages using &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTML&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HTML&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cascading_Style_Sheets&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;CSS&lt;/a&gt;. I remember them being really ugly, but I learnt a lot from it. I started understanding the structure of the pages I was visiting frequently - facebook, google, wikipedia, etc. Though the code was tough to read, I managed to understand it a bit. And eventually, my understanding of web pages and sites started to become good ( I wasn’t familiar with any backend stuff back then, so I didn’t know what happened behind the scenes on those sites ).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then came &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/C_(programming_language)&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;C&lt;/a&gt; - the language that introduced me to Errors and Debugging. There were errors in QBASIC, but the code I used to write back then was so minimal and small, there wasn’t a huge scope for good errors. But with C, everything changed. There were segmentation faults, type errors, logical errors and what not. This helped me learn how the computer worked behind the scenes. As C is a language that is closer to the system, I would recommend first-timers to start with a language like C, but more on that later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later on, I learnt &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/C++&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;C++&lt;/a&gt; from the book ‘C++ For Dummies, 7&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; Edition’. Then I learnt the concepts of object oriented programming. I remember how happy I was, when my code of a banking system finally worked, wherein you would be able to create accounts, login, credit and debit money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I learnt &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/JavaScript&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;JavaScript&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Java_(programming_language)&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; in my 12&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; class. It was taught as a part of our curriculum, but I learnt more than that. What the teachers taught was very simple, basically it was what I learnt with C, the only differance now was that of the language.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Halfway through my 12&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; class, entered &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/PHP&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;PHP&lt;/a&gt;. PHP intrigued me a lot as it helped me out of the dead-looking Console window, and into the browsers. I started off simply - fetching data from databases and displaying, and inserting data into the databases using forms. Then I created a user management system, which handled the login, registration and sessions of users. My final project using PHP was called “Veroyo” ( modified from “True me” in italian ), which was a social networking site, where it had a user management system and a posts management system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I got enrolled into IIITV, and my way of learning stuff changed. But more on that later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adios folks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 19:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/learn/coding/2018/09/02/journey-before-iiitv.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/learn/coding/2018/09/02/journey-before-iiitv.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>learn</category>
        
        <category>coding</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>blog.init();</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;consoleloghello-world&quot;&gt;console.log(“Hello World”);&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;first-ever-blog-post&quot;&gt;First Ever Blog Post!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone! I am Jay Mistry, a Sophomore at IIIT Vadodara. This is my first ever blog post! I am very excited regarding this blog &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;rossoskull.me&lt;/code&gt;, because now I have a tool, that’s under my control, using which I will share some ( or many ) of the cool stuff that happens in my life. Hopefully, these blog posts will be helpful to some of you in one way or the other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To know more about me, you can go &lt;a href=&quot;/about/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Also to get more updates about this blog, or from my life, you can follow me on various social medias.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-this-blog&quot;&gt;About This Blog&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog is created using &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;, which is a tool that helps you create simple, blog-aware static sites! Sounds cool, doesn’t it? Guess what, it actually is. This site is hosted using &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com/&quot;&gt;Github Pages&lt;/a&gt;, and that too - for free! GitHub Pages supports Jekyll. I’ll be sharing my experiences and some stuff about coding using this blog.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 11:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/learn/coding/2018/08/31/blog-init.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/learn/coding/2018/08/31/blog-init.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>learn</category>
        
        <category>coding</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
