<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rossoskull.me</title>
    <description>Hey everyone! I am Jay Mistry, a sophomore at IIIT Vadodara. I got into coding a bit early in
 my life, and am loving it since then! I love learning new stuff, and building things that help 
 out me, and others. I believe in building a solution, rather than finding it someplace else. You 
 can know more about me on one of my social handles. Thanks for visiting!
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 22:33:30 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 22:33:30 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>blog.init();</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;consoleloghello-world&quot;&gt;console.log(“Hello World”);&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;first-ever-blog-post&quot;&gt;First Ever Blog Post!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone! I am Jay Mistry, a Sophomore at IIIT Vadodara. This is my first ever blog post! I am very excited regarding this blog &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;rossoskull.me&lt;/code&gt;, because now I have a tool, that’s under my control, using which I will share some ( or many ) of the cool stuff that happens in my life. Hopefully, these blog posts will be helpful to some of you in one way or the other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To know more about me, you can follow me on various social medias.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-this-blog&quot;&gt;About This Blog&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog is created using &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;, which is a tool that helps you create simple, blog-aware static sites! Sounds cool, doesn’t it? Guess what, it actually is. This site is hosted using &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com/&quot;&gt;Github Pages&lt;/a&gt;, and that too - for free! GitHub Pages supports Jekyll. I’ll be sharing my experiences and some stuff about coding using this blog.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 11:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/learn/coding/2018/08/31/blog-init.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/learn/coding/2018/08/31/blog-init.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>learn</category>
        
        <category>coding</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
